Okay, we are now going to all the order of the City Council meeting for today's day and
time.
Item 2 is public input and unscheduled personal approaches, you know, in the arts, we should
just address the council on any of the agenda items.
There are being non item 3 is consent agenda, staff is recommending items 4 through 9 for the
consent agenda.
I just got one comment on that, okay.
There is in regards to item 7, and I know we discussed at the last meeting that we
was going to take that to the CBB and we did and I appreciate can be in there.
I just want to touch everybody that we did speak to the CBB board and we're recommending
a personal recommendation.
It's recommending a personal approval of that, so if there's no comment on any of the other
items, do we have most of your approval of the consent agenda?
Second.
Roll call please.
Johnson.
Forester.
High.
Weston.
Lewis.
I chose.
Item 10 is presentation by Arrogens Associates of the fiscal year of 1617, Arrogant Financial
Statements and the Independent, Arrogant Property Report.
How are you?
We appreciate you making the drive up.
I hope you are warm on your way back.
Okay.
This was great.
I'm not sure there's very warm.
There's very warm.
There's very much good.
My name is Andy Komer.
I'm a CPA and I'm talking about Arrogant Associates.
We're at an Edmund.
We did you on its many years ago and then come back this is our second year since May, years.
So you should have two documents in front of you.
One is a big thing.
One of your actual annual financial statements.
The other one is a required communication waiver.
If you don't have enough, okay.
I don't like to make you go through it.
Read it.
I mean, because there's a couple of things I just want to tell you.
And I've got my notes on you.
But the first thing is, Arrogant Associates.
Essentially, we have two reports in here.
And then the rest of us, that is just your financial information.
The first one is the Autopinian where we say, your financial statements are literally correct.
So it's what we call a cleanup bin in an amount of part of the bin.
That's what the state wants to see.
That's what you end this out to does with the expectancy and lawlessness.
So there's no modifications to that.
Just to stand and report.
Then there's also a second report, if you want to hurry back.
That's required by the state of Oklahoma.
That means the tax activity.
And it's essentially, kind of, there's two things.
One is your internal control.
So if there's issues with your internal control that we want to comment on.
That's what we would put that in here.
The second section deals with compliance with laws of regulations.
And you might say, compliance with law laws.
It can be compliance with the laws of the state of Oklahoma.
And you can just be compliance with laws of the land.
Maybe your own policies that you want.
So anything type of compliance that's significant, those issues will be back here.
So there's nothing back there.
So the letters there, but there's nothing on it, you know, to those kind of issues.
So that's good, and that's what you call it.
But just one lecture would be a word on that.
Then as far as the actual numbers and I'll just briefly
on about this and if you don't have questions at all and I'll address it
by the amount of kittis, kittis, kittis, kittis, kittis, kittis.
If we just look into the general fun of myself, you've got about
about two months worth of fun bags.
You know, if you can pair it to revenues.
And so this doesn't mean kittis, you rainy day fun.
It's just your general fun.
And so I think the general idea is to have three to six months.
Yeah, it's a great place to be.
So you're very close to that.
So I don't think that's a concern.
And especially before you're rainy day fun, you know,
how did you find kittis at that, but you can be low over that.
So I think you're doing a well there.
The spot has the utilities and I know I couldn't quite
get all of that, but I heard it come up a few times, but you
have utility fund.
You've got about a $4 million profit before, and you know,
you start moving money on the $20 funds.
So just a little, just a tad under $4 million.
So that seems to be doing very well.
You know, the rates in the general institution of capital,
you know, so it can do its business.
And I keep going.
So really, those are really, you know, two primary funds,
a job fund and a utility fund.
And so both of those appear to be done well.
And of course, you have to do wherever you're rainy day fun.
So really, that's kind of this report in that show.
I have a couple of questions.
I did not make sure if this was for you or Dean Houd.
I'm doing the qualitative aspects that there's a sentence.
It starts out effect your July one, the single implement
new accounting standard regarding its post-employment benefits.
I'm assuming that's retirement.
It's retirement, it's any kind of a,
anything you want to occur on post-employment,
it's sure it's going to be anything you want it on.
And what are the accounting changes being made and why?
Are they being made because the federal government said,
we need to do it differently or the same?
Well, this comes from, there's a separate body that
moves in the new jersey or the, that issues accounting standards.
Right, guys, the governmental accounting standards board.
They're the official group that says, here's how you need to have things.
So you've got your pension plan,
you know, please don't fire them at the city plan.
The forward, well, now those, the police and the fire are both under fun.
And so now each city has to report their portion of that unfunded liability.
And now, so that's an effect.
And now, this hope that this is what your portion of the post-employment benefits.
that relates to your health insurance.
And in that most cities, and you include most cities,
well, once their employee gets retirement age,
they can retire, but stay on the insurance plan.
And pay them some rent, they don't wait for free.
They got to pay for them.
But the right that of that retiree is paying
as a subsidized fee.
It's lower than what they would pay on their own
in a free morning.
Because they've got younger people,
you know, help them bring that right down there.
They're up there, the oldest in.
So they've got younger people,
help them blend that right.
And so, guys, because now, said, you've got your parents
and expenses, people go along,
and we want to recognize the livelihood of you for that.
You're not going to pay for that until they get to time.
And it's kind of hard to grasp if I get that.
And if you don't, it's okay.
But it's new.
And it's going to hit next year.
Well, they're year and night.
And usually, that's, it depends on kind of view of it.
Usually, it's a decent size number.
And that liability will be, you know,
it could be a couple of million islands.
But it's, I mean, it's not like it's 10,000 dollars.
Right.
And so, we really want to know the actual,
we'll have to get the parents that in and when we learn that,
we'll be able to get them out of the car.
So it's nothing that the city is done differently
or wrong or poorly, it's just a reflection
of the change in the counting standards.
OK.
On page 200 other matters, there's RSI,
consent responses to inquiries, does that have an acronym?
But what does that acronym represent?
States for, uh, where do you, where is that?
We're going to find something more information.
RSI, yes.
OK.
But I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't.
That's OK.
That's what I'm doing next.
But RSI, there's, states for required
supplemental information, and so there are things
and here.
Again, it's just, kind of, kind of, I've
wrong and technical with how that all means,
all things and good things.
But as the sources of some supplemental schedules,
that are not part of the typical set of financial statements,
but gas BSS, you've got to do it anyway.
And really, it relates to the pension plan,
in a specific way, the place in fire plants.
So you can see, you know, how those plans are funded,
what you share those plans is, you're just one
C, yeah, hundreds of cities that are in those plans.
And so how much of that whole unfunded liability
are you all receiving and how much, you know,
the same as that means, what's back there?
And then in C, you know, C, you're increased our reserves
for uncollectable utility receivables by 470,000.
I mean, that's not all.
That didn't all happen one year.
We just increase in the reserves.
What happened is, we're going to fall back there for a second.
There's a self-association from a doctor's association.
It's a lot of my experience.
For example, they're in Worcester's kind of boss and you're there.
But they help the city get ready for the day.
They might help you just there in the air.
But then they come up at the air in and help you get ready for a lot of the day.
They actually prefer to get ready for the day before.
And then we literally make changes in whatever.
But they come up with part of that pre-automatic.
They've adjusted the...
The...
It's pretty much just the calculation of the way that it's done here.
And so the calculation was done when they posted the entry.
They got posted backwards.
And so this 470 is really the double effect.
Just to get it on your right way.
If that makes sense.
It's really the actual entry within 3,000 or so.
And so keep in mind also that you all like,
virtually in the other city, you never really ride off or receive them.
You know, most couples at some point actually ride off.
And so they're...
They're around.
So that can't just doesn't get bigger throughout.
Because you're constantly trying those receipts.
You're receiving those receipts.
You're constantly getting bigger.
Because you never ride one off.
You know, if someone moves back, you can be able to use the ropes.
You know, if they move out with that.
So really that's why this thing is just still getting bigger.
So every year there's going to be some adjustment.
Just because every year you're receiving them.
But we have things.
That's just a little bit down.
Right.
So a period of time.
You've been in the best home.
And all you're doing the 470 is really just correcting the entry.
I mean, they made it entry based on their calculation of what it was going to be or projected to be.
They've just to mistake and the way they did that.
So you're correcting that posting is what that represents.
Okay.
So before I forget, the Crawford's do a very good job.
And we work with them on a number of cities.
But we're a total of our separate forms.
Separate ownership, separate forms.
It's definitely a deal.
And one of them, they are.
They do a very good job.
And yes, what we mean.
So certainly enjoy working with them as well.
Questions?
Is there an action item here?
Green?
Which is a presentation.
What we just have a presentation.
Okay.
Mr. Crawford.
Thank you for your time.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
I have a safe feedback.
I'm 11.
How could you choose proposal for any Georgian or what?
We talked about this.
Briefly at the last meeting.
And I know that it was absent.
So we wanted to carry it forward to this meeting and give everybody an opportunity to think about some of the comments that Georgian had made.
And think about it differently.
ideas and I don't know I have something to say I don't know if you have something you
want to answer my time or if you just come in that because you feel like you're supposed to.
No, I'm just here that's terrible.
Any questions you want to have to read if they need so.
Okay.
So I think last time there were some concerns about establishing a precedent that would
didn't create potential exposure to the city from the long list of contractors that we
have because currently Georgia is a contractor.
As distinct from, say, Chuck and Glen were a contract in Poeese.
And so if that is concerned, one of the ways around that concern, I'd talk with Kim about
this a little bit, would be establishing Georgia and as a contract in Poeese and much in
the way that Chuck and Glen are.
One of the other issues related to that was, okay, how much if we did that, how much Georgia
and how much work is she going to do and is that going to be enough to offset the value of that
benefit.
And so I talked with Kim again just a little bit before the meeting and I think from our conversation
in Georgia and what you were interested in was family coverage, right?
Yeah.
If it was available.
Is that right?
Right.
But as I understand it, I would be the only one for him, the city only pays for its employee and then
the employee that it lets to pay the difference for that.
That's the way it currently works for city employees.
Now the total amount of that coverage including the city, the employees coverage which
is 660 and then the additional coverage for the family would be $1,368.
If you divided that by Georgia's current contract or rate with the city of $150 now, that's
basically nine hours a month is what?
In order to basically cover those costs, that's what Georgia would have to work on behalf
of the city.
And I think Dean had indicated the last meeting that he felt comfortable at least in the
next 12 months period that we would need her services or the services of some outside
attorney at least that amount.
Good.
Nine hours above what I was doing this last year.
That's what you mean right?
No, I just mean nine hours total.
So $1,368 divided by 150 is this is nine hours at your current rate.
And so what I have done is asking me what I'm trying to do is get that.
Express for everybody the various concerns that came up and then if there's a consensus
On the council I would ask me all to
Work with Kim to develop a puzzle that would be submitted to the council for consideration and I've just outlined the two points
That I remember coming up as concerned. I don't know if there were others
And if there are, then we certainly want to talk about
How many hours do you ever have reach a month now?
Well in calendar year
So that of course crossed the city's fiscal year because I started in the end of January last year
It was about 17 to 18 hours a month
And as I explained in my letter, I think some of that was held down a little bit by the fact that I had baby in March
And then of course I was dealing with a lot of backlog after that, but so I think both my capacity is greater this year and
Dean advises that
The need will be greater this year. I have I
Manalized it in terms of if we increased if I did
More hours I did some of that
Would go to cover
This cost for the city and then these primary new capital projects that we have
Water to the street through
So there is one point for the west end of the budget
Yeah, I have primarily done
Real estate issues and the
Contract sort of business side issues and where there is
Overlapped between that and more according to the government side ben and I bring more together
I guess I shouldn't speak for that
For my rather presumptuous
In all I'm trying to promise tonight is determined if there's at least a consensus on the council that we want
to
Consider a proposal and also articulate
For since deals agreed to
Carry that water so to speak if we do
Artigulate for him any other concern besides a couple of things that I am
And if there are no others and it would just be a question in the allergic consensus
I think if I can talk you know
One of the things that I had concerned with is, like you said, on the face of it, it's hard
to do this to where I know you got a lot of 32-hour a week and please don't have that
option.
So I struggle with that, but then I look at it as, you know, I shouldn't punish somebody if they're
doing a job force.
But I look at how do we, you know, one of the things we always talk about, is how do we know
what you're doing?
I'm not saying you're not doing it, by all means it's been proven.
But it's how do we grade somebody and, you know, how do we know who's in charge of that?
Who's overseeing and unlisted?
Well, Dean wasn't clarifying what's getting done and what's getting passed.
So you know, I struggle with that, but I really have a hard time with a lot of people that
would, you know, work for the city that don't get this option, so it's where I really would
like and I appreciate you stepping up and working.
I don't want to, I feel very uneasy about changing our healthcare plan because I know that
was mentioned that it could, and I want to, I like to know what changes those are and that's
where I struggle with it, but I can't, could you come up, please?
I just want to echo what Brian said, and that's why, if it is, it is, it can change as long
to the council that you all want me to do this and talk with him and see if we can work
up and how I think we'll have to do that, but if not, it's going to work, that is.
So there are a lot of importantness depending on how we do this.
So what this one day was given opportunity, I get to down the field and we can look at some
different scenarios and what that would mean and could be more specific with you about what
that would be.
We've talked about the change to the health-land document would be if we were going to offer a
contractor assistance, which we've talked about is probably going to open up kind of a
family response that we don't want to get out, but if we're talking about a contract employee,
then there wouldn't be any change to the health-land document.
It's no different than what we do for a municipal judge, but we get this done together
and we're going to answer those questions there.
Right, and I think the mayor's touched on my, and that's the stuff I, and I do call a
Chuck Chestnut because I had to frame the reference and ask him how many hours he works
a month and he said, the 2020 and 25 is depending on last week, they were in four, for five
hours because we go a lot of tickets, but he said it fluctuates between 2020 and 25 or
month is what he felt comfortable, and he has to make a new work.
You know, and you look at the 17 hours I believe is what you put, what you said at 150 and then
if you drop it at 2125 and you jump up to 28, you do get an increase there of, you know,
just under $1,000 and that kind of awful.
that you're $900 and some dollars. So I see where that's going. But I would feel comfortable
if you're willing to step up and do that to see what our options are. I would like to, I would personally like to do that.
I think it's pretty much often George Ann's shoes for a minute. If there's a way to do this
where there's a, let's just say you're a contract employee for I'm using 10 hours because nine hours
for us, you know, did the math a few minutes ago. You're better off because then all of that comes out pretty
tax. If you have to pay some of that then you have to pay it with after tax dollars. And so to the extent that
if something gets worked out it can be structured in that way to just better off. I mean, I mean that's
cost to see to anything in that respect, it just saves her tax dollars. Just like any of us now that are paying,
you know, our premiums pre-tacks. So just from a structural standpoint keep that in mind, it would be
her benefit and the cost to the city as far as that goes. So what you're asking us to do is give our blessing for
me all to save like the more I can see if we can work this out. Okay. Everybody give it that. Yeah.
Okay. I'm good with that. I understand Brian's concerns. I just need to know if you all have concerns.
It's something we need to do. My concern is she needs to be a contract employee before we even offer insurance
because if we just do it to am I saying that right? Yeah. I think I completely. I think Kim was made clear that we
could want to we don't want to mess with our family. So the only way is the only way is going to work,
I think is if we're able to work out the work out situation where she's a contract employee like Chuck
Ann. Ben? Yeah. I just want to point out that if that is the way that you decide to proceed and all the way to work for
the industry. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay.
He would draw off all the paperwork. George Ann wouldn't be involved in drawing up or what she's
she mentioned last time to that she wouldn't be involved drawing up her own. Her own deal. It works out that way.
No, I agree. I'd like to let you dig into little deeper and see what you know well options we have.
I mean you're taking it to another level of adding position that has to be maintained and
accountant for what they do and I just want to make sure that how do we address that? That's all I want.
That's not a problem. I thought I just want to make sure that we
will end to your point and maybe I'm going to talk about this earlier that we're addressed.
saying they're contract employing now and we first had a candle and bad in the election and
we started like that, that's something we didn't put off, I put off, but that's your concern.
Well, and also I am fully in favor of accountability because I think that makes everybody
better as they do, but as I see it kind of the way the city's structure I would be reporting
to Ben, I mean I'm reported to Ben right now anyway, but that's he would be, I mean Ben is
the head of the legal department and you always want that far away from me at the end of the
end.
For that, and honestly I have no problem with that, I just want to make sure that that's
outlined and that's put forth and how do we know we're getting that 20 out of what, you know,
the people out there feel comfortable and we're going to offer this, feel we're getting
our 28 hours and if we can do that, we're going to do that.
You're just saying 28 hours, for example, make sure, yes, because what was presented.
Okay, thank you Jordan.
I think him and Neil are playing on meeting next Monday, and after both of the day we have
some something back to a break with whatever that might be.
Okay, good day.
See if I can find my idea.
Item 12, ordinance 2018-02, I'm ending the rainy day fun, basically, and I know we talked about
this some before June, or fresh our memory please.
So at the last meeting, we talked about some changes to the 28 day fun.
You all brought out in the discussion that we had that you wanted it to be very, very clear
and the new ordinance that, to withdraw money from the rainy day fun, will require the majority
of the board and has to do this.
So we didn't run into a situation where, for instance, there were only three council members present.
So we had a forum, and then two of those three, which is less than half the door, the board
approves withdrawing money from the deal.
So I went back in and made that one change, where we were, and it simply provides that
the required majority of the entire board, whatever board consists of at that one time,
saying right now we have five, so we require at least three to be able to withdraw money from that.
And that's really the only change that we have in what you have before it's in the eye for what it's going to look like we have at the last
Any questions for being on that?
Okay, we have a most jeopardy
What do you think?
Second, roll ball
Johnson
Forester
Lewis, I'm Schultz
I'm 13, also engineering master agreement for stone, stone, covert, processing
That's set around
Alicia
Yes, sir
As you all know
Excuse me
We are working on this flash pad
We wanted the things that we had talked about
Was where we can join
Joe Paul, which is down here
And with the flash pad and of course this is prior to the building being demolished
We had come up with also a pretty one here
And you'll notice this is the parking lot and this is the parking lot for Joe Paul
We will make this into a
We're calling it a bridge drainage cover
We'll be able to drive our
Maybe it's equipment over
If we had a truck or something that we need to drive over it to get to in front of would be able to do that
Mainly it would be a pedestrian crossing so that people can park at the Joe Paul parking lot
We'll be able to walk over and get to our splash pad
We also are looking at doing this one here
This is public works right here
Right now in order to do the moving or maintenance or anything of any of these we have to get out onto the road
From all the way around and take care of it
If we want to do any maintenance to Joe Paul and you have to drive all the way around
This would give us access and he or our equipment
We're not going to drive onto the road and it just makes much much more sense
In order to be able to do that
That's where we're closing the night the workowner
So that also can start what we need to do to get that started
One of the things that Sean would like to do is
Kind of explore some some good options as far as cost-effectiveness and things like that
We do want a concrete box at the large area
Dean made a very good point this is a part you want it to look
You want it to look nice you don't want just you know you're your round
Corgated steel in there where it doesn't look hard for the
But we also want it very usable and friendly in that sense
So it wouldn't be a concrete box
So at least you can go back over there please
So first a small one you're just going to put a cover in there
And some just make it what you can track because that's a great channel
Is that a big one?
I'm going to put it up all the way to get it to stop, and we're going to be on gate here.
And so are these trees still there or go that's what I thought that's what I thought.
So, so it's all clear it out and you're just going, there's a quick, it flows through there also.
The drainage comes right through here, comes down, comes to the side, runs underneath,
D3, and on that way, it carries a significant amount of water.
Because it collects the water from across mainstream, and it comes, like I said,
under, under and here, and around.
So, one of the key things we want to make sure of this, we'll do this project for our inadvertently creating a dam.
Yes.
Which is also higher in hearing comes in to the water.
Can we make sure that we keep that water flowing?
Yes.
You know, it's a planning commission meeting, and they brought up an interesting point about a fence to keep the kids out of there.
I know that you said that the grant that we had was for the splash pad itself.
It doesn't cover a fence, but I used to work at that building, and when you get heavy rains, it's a splash flood behind that.
Hopefully, no kids would be back there during that time, but that was a concern of the plan commission.
Very, very important about keeping children out of there, and that's something that we are looking at now.
The plan commission isn't awesome.
You're talking about the questions that we don't think about, and they're very good questions.
It's actually, you guys came up with how would you access one to the other, so that's what better started on this.
And then also, it is still in the plan for the water off of the splash pad to go into that creek, and it's okay.
You guys still have to do this and retain the salt and then like that when you take care of it.
Okay.
Well, the water coming off the splash pad is not going to be an additional water that's going to be coming while it's raining or heavy rains,
because it's going to be like that.
It probably will be a minute.
It will be water that's where it's going to, you know, be like that.
Okay.
That's why why not does theirs?
They'll be a little creek to break.
And keep them on this.
It's just a bottle of tap water.
It's what's right on.
That's treated.
We're going to blow it back.
We're going to start you getting anything.
Other than, so it comes out of your cap.
How long is this?
What are we looking at on this?
To take place?
It's a much, much, much shorter than the highway 125.
Yes.
Okay.
It's still a check.
This isn't going to slow down the opening of the pad, right?
No.
Hopefully this will help.
Maybe get it rolling.
This also, Dean had mentioned before, ODEEQ being able to do some remediation, and they're
like they've done in our other park down there.
This will help that because it joins these as one park.
That was one of the hangups that ODEEQ had was because that was an industrial side.
This is a park and we'll now be joining them together to make them into one of the things.
So we need to pass any kind of ordinance, guesignating that as a park, and as at the process,
or as it is, you know, we address the issue of how does a park look at a park, and there's
really not a lot to it that didn't even be designated as an park, but another area that we're
talking about, the original stat hard work made for these.
So I mean, as if you need it, it doesn't need you going to blame something before us.
Now, while you can make sure that we get help from ODEEQ, that's necessary.
Well, I don't point out that the mayor has to wait as much upon, if it sounds good.
We could possibly see that there's a proper mention to make it happen, or it would be a reunion.
Okay.
Do that for us.
Kind of assuming that's going to all go through parks and rec, or, of course, they be in all that
on the side of that.
A lot of different parks and rec work, of course.
Why are there, of course, are also going to mention that next week, we're bringing the
question for the council.
Yes.
Well, the recommendation of the committee for the architect.
So we're going to be there while you'll be considering that, actually.
I mean, the reason I'm bringing this up is that however you feel about the laws of having drugs
within 500 feet, or 1,000 feet, or 2,000 feet of a park, I would assume that there's some legal
designation that makes something a park or not.
And so, I think we need to make sure we do that.
Do you need a motion player?
Yes.
So we're going to order the word for us.
And second.
We'll probably.
Johnson.
Lewis.
I.
Western.
Forester.
I.
Thank you.
I'm 14 new business in any new business.
I'm 15.
Staff reports, which are in your packet.
They're available if you have questions.
Yeah.
And then the election would you mind on a picture on the spot on the what's going on down
and shelters that's playing warming there and during this cold.
It is.
A little human because we're, you know, we're still playing things out, so there's some water in there,
but.
It stay in warm it.
It's working as it.
It was expected to do.
We've had a little bit of trouble with our quarantine shelter, but we've got that fixed right now.
where we've got good heat in there and old unit and the heat strips and just gone
and so we got that take place.
We have moved the cast, I don't know if you've been in there, we closed off the wall
that was the bright room and opened up the wall to the medical room to what was the
bright room to expand that and that made a little out of the medical room and that's
what we're keeping the cast now.
They're completely away from all of the dogs and there are far away from the dogs as
you have them in that particular shelter, so we still have to go.
We stay at the absolute of the dogs, we're getting ready to move 9 to a rescue this
coming third day night though, so we've had relatively few calls, I've just
been seeing stuff so bad here in the game, relatively few calls since it's gotten
really cooler out, but we do stay pretty steady with what calls I think.
Speaking of, don't go away, speaking of relatively few calls with the recent weather issues
as a couple of days, I know there's not much you can do on some of the first day
to snow, but I know today the streets were getting much better, and I know you've
got some crews out working on that, so I appreciate staff for doing that.
That's right, I'm so proud.
Yeah, that's just what it was.
Yes, they started at 6.30 yesterday morning and ran into 11 o'clock last night, went home and
came back at four o'clock and we kind of staggered them a little bit today and ran into four
o'clock and then we'll come back in at 6.37 o'clock tomorrow morning and started, the weather
is pretty clear as far as our main main right now.
Our problem is, is once it starts getting cold and you've got water on those roads, then it turns
into black eyes.
How can we need this mean?
It's just what you're saying, once we leave this mean here and here and here and here and here.
Please be careful, yes, so.
Thank you, sir.
We'll have this mean, he has a brain, couldn't make it through.
Okay, Mayor and Council, Mayor and Council believe in the accidents in the other direction.
It's called outside city manager communication.
Very quickly, it's called to provide you a steady session.
That's good.
It's called to be at 4.30.
It'll be 25 degrees and like something we said, please be careful at home because it's
Did you make a most Georgia?
Do you want me to?
Yes.
I'll make a most Georgia.
And I'll suck it.
Well, it's all.